Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/paolaquevedo-98212381 (LinkedIn) www.artstation.com/andyqvdo (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Internet Protocol Suite (TCP/IP)
Python (Programming Language)
Front-end Development

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Innovative Uses of Artificial Intelligence

Honors-Awards 2016 Spring Show

Paola Quevedo

MS Computer Science Student at Northeastern University Fremont, California, United States

Summary

I'm a Venezuelan graduate student in Computer Science from Northeastern University. I have an associate degree in Graphic Design and worked for 3 years in Web Design and Development. In 2014, I decided to come to the United States to pursue my bachelors in 3D Modeling for Games. While working as a 3D modeler, I realized I wanted to be more involved in the engineering aspects of my field, eventually this led me to pursue a master in Computer Science. My current goals are to learn as much as I can from the program, industry experts, and my peers, and ultimately get the opportunity to do a co-op/internship to further acquire knowledge and experience.

Experience

Meta

Network Engineer
June 2022 - Present (11 months)

Menlo Park, California, United States

Facebook Network Engineer May 2021 - August 2021 (4 months) San Francisco Bay Area

Linden Lab Art Intern June 2019 - November 2019 (6 months) San Francisco Bay Area

· Contributed on the relaunch of Project Sansar by building and texturing 3d environmental content such as props, foliage, and modular assets following a PBR workflow and adapting to the performance constraints required by the virtual reality platform.

- · Worked directly with art director and lead environment artist to create, optimize and prepare 3d assets, textures, collisions, and animation content to implement into Sansar's proprietary engine.
- · Assisted the Art Director and department leads with research and presentation assembly tasks.

Venture Games

3D Artist

September 2019 - October 2019 (2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

- · Created in-game 3D assets following the art style established for the project.
- · Worked closely with the Game Engineering Lead to build assets that met the technical

constraints for a mobile game.

· UV and textured assets using Substance Painter and Photoshop.

AAU StudioX

3D Artist

June 2017 - May 2018 (1 year)

San Francisco Bay Area

- · Collaborated with a team of artists to create a mobile VR experience of the Four Freedoms exhibition from the Norman Rockwell Museum.
- · Worked on Tony DiTerlizzi's Magic Mirror project to bring several of his characters into Virtual Reality.
- · Responsible for the creation and optimization of 3D environment assets based on concept art and referential images.
- Coordinated technical strategies with Art Director based on game engine constraints.
- · Worked with riggers to prepare assets to be sent along the production pipeline.

Grupo ICT, C.A.

3 years 6 months

Web Developer

November 2011 - January 2014 (2 years 3 months)

Venezuela

· Developed dynamic websites in HTML5/CSS3 integrating data from back-end services and databases such as PHP and MySQL.

- · Built custom content management solution for customers' easy maintenance of their web properties.
- · Managed and coordinated graphic and web development projects from concept design to development for a variety of customers:

IndustriAvicola

- · Built and managed the organization's website using HTML, CSS, and PHP. Collaborated with the graphic design team to conceive concept design based on requirements. Responsible for continuos update of the website's content.
- · Created art concept for magazine advertisement.

Ajeven

· Designed, developed, and produced six websites for the side brands of the company; using HTML, CSS, CSS3, HTML5, and PHP programming languages. Worked with a team of three persons to complete this project under a seven-months deadline with two video editions and a thematic coloring game built with Flash

Detsa S.A.

· Created corporate identity using Illustrator, to help the company to establish and open offices in a new country. Produced logo and stationary resources based on the company's history and the essence of the new cultural market.

ICT, C.A

- · Analysis and study of company's history to design a corporate identity package which included logos for the group of companies, stationary, id cards, t-shirts, and website.
- · Design of newspaper ad of the company's product line with Photoshop.
- · Photography, edition, design, and animation of a product catalog of the product line using Photoshop, Illustrator, and Flash.

Kentucky University

· Design of event banner for an IEEE Tech Conference with Illustrator.

Excessus bar

· Designed thematic flyers with Photoshop and Illustrator for diverse events of the nightclub.

Project Assistant

August 2010 - November 2011 (1 year 4 months)

Valencia, Carabobo, Venezuela

- Assisted network field engineers in coordinating the implementation of Cisco switching, routing and firewall solutions.
- Assisted coordination and deployment of structured cabling projects.

Education

Northeastern University

Master of Science - MS, Computer Science · (2020 - 2022)

Academy of Art University

Bachelor's Degree, Animation & Visual Effects, Graphic Design · (2015 - May 2019)

Instituto de Diseño de Valencia

Associate's degree, Graphic Design · (2007 - 2010)